<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Project01</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>

    <string name="terms">
    "Welcome to XIO! These Terms and Conditions outline the rules and regulations for using our
        mobile application. By downloading, installing, or using XIO, you agree to comply with these
        Terms.If you do not agree, please refrain from using the app.

    1. Acceptance of Terms
    By accessing or using XIO, you confirm that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by
        these Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy. If you are using the app on behalf of a
        company or organization, you represent that you have the authority to bind that entity to
        these Terms.

    2. Description of the Service
    XIO is designed to assist electric vehicle (EV) owners by providing features such as:

    Locating Charging Stations: Find nearby EV charging stations based on your GPS location.
    Charging Session Tracking: Monitor and manage your charging sessions, including duration and costs.
    User Community Features: Connect with other EV users to share information and experiences.
    Alerts and Notifications: Receive real-time alerts for charging station availability and special
    offers.

    3. User Permissions
    To provide the above services effectively, XIO requests certain permissions from your device:

    GPS Location: Access to your GPS location is essential for identifying nearby charging stations
        and providing real-time updates. You can manage this permission in your device settings.

    Contacts: This permission may be required to allow users to share information about charging
        stations with their contacts. You can opt out of this permission, but certain features may be limited.

    Camera Access: If XIO includes QR code scanning for charging stations, we will request access
        to your camera.

    Storage Access: To enhance user experience, we may need access to your device's storage for
        saving user preferences and session data.

    By granting these permissions, you acknowledge that you understand how we will use the information
        collected and agree to provide access as necessary for the app’s functionality.

    4. User Responsibilities
    As a user of XIO, you agree to:

    Use the app only for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms.
    Provide accurate, current, and complete information during registration
    and keep your account information up to date.
    Maintain the confidentiality of your account credentials and not share them with others.
    Notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security.
    Not engage in any activity that disrupts or interferes with the app’s functionality or other
        users' access.
    5. Data Collection and Usage
    We are committed to protecting your privacy. Our data collection practices are detailed in our
        Privacy Policy. We may collect:

    Personal Information: This includes your name, email address, and other contact information when
        you register or use certain features.
    Location Data: To provide personalized services, we collect location data when the app is in use.
    Usage Data: We track how the app is used to improve our services and user experience.
    By using XIO, you consent to our data collection and usage practices as outlined in our Privacy
        Policy.

    6. Intellectual Property
    All content, features, and functionality in XIO, including but not limited to text, graphics,
    logos, icons, and software, are the exclusive property of [Your Company Name] or our licensors.
    These materials are protected by copyright, trademark, and other intellectual property laws. You may not reproduce, modify, distribute, or otherwise use any of the materials without our prior written consent.

    7. Limitation of Liability
    To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, [Your Company Name] shall not be liable for
    any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages, including but not
    limited to loss of profits, data, or other intangible losses, resulting from your use or inability
    to use XIO.

    8. Termination
    We reserve the right to terminate or suspend your access to XIO at our sole discretion, without
    prior notice, for any reason, including if you violate these Terms. Upon termination, your right
    to use the app will immediately cease.

    9. Changes to Terms
    We may update these Terms and Conditions from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by
    posting the new Terms on this page and updating the effective date at the top. Your continued
    use of XIO after any changes constitutes acceptance of the revised Terms.

    10. Governing Law
    These Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of
    [Your Jurisdiction]. Any disputes arising under or in connection with these Terms shall be
    subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in [Your Jurisdiction].

    11. Contact Us
    If you have any questions or concerns regarding these Terms and Conditions, please contact us at:

    Email: [Your Email Address]
    Phone: [Your Phone Number]
    Address: [Your Company Address]
    12. Entire Agreement
    These Terms and Conditions, along with our Privacy Policy, constitute the entire agreement
    between you and [Your Company Name] regarding your use of XIO and supersede any prior agreements. "
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
</resources>